# Sendy Halim

Jl. Krendang Timur No. 5B West Jakarta 11260 Phone +6281291766088 Email sendyhalim93@gmail.com



### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

A programming enthusiast with high curiosity. Have been in love with programming since 2010, love to learn new things, technologies and always excited to be part of a team. High self-discipline and responsibility, strong dedication and a good team player, able to work in high deadlines and cross-functional team, hard-worker.

#### **EDUCATION**

2014	Graha Akuntan, IAI Knowledge Center
	Taxation Brevet AB
2011-now	Bunda Mulia University
	Accounting Major, Cumulative GPA 3.57
2008-2011	Ricci 1 Senior high school
2005-2008	Ricci 1 Junior high school
2005-2008	LBPP LIA Batu tulis
	English course
1999-2005	Ricci 1 Elementary school
1999-2005	Manhattan English Course
	English course
1997-1999	TK Ricci 1
	Kindergarten and Preschools

#### **EXPERIENCE**

January 2012-now	Freelance programmer
	Develop web application stack with given specifications including web
	application, database system, linux server, content delivery network, and search
	engine optimization.
August 2013 - December 2013	Backend and Frontend Web programmer at CV Upwardstech
	Develop web application stack, create modular testable code, and reporting
	application progress.

#### **SKILLS**

- Javascript (AngularJS, JQuery, NodeJS, RequireJS, GruntJS)
- PHP (Laravel, Codelgniter)
- Test Driven Development (Unit testing, Functional testing, Acceptance testing)
- HTML

- CSS
- Version Control System (Git Version Control)
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Able to normalize and write Structured Query Language on MySQL and PostgreSQL (Fluent)
- Deep Object Oriented Programming knowledge
- Object Oriented Programming design patterns
- Modular programming with Dependency Injection / Inversion of Control
- Basic knowledge of Java, Python, C++
- Familiar with Linux terminal
- Accounting (IFRS)
- Tax

## **ACTIVITIES/VOLUNTEER**

Content writer at sendyhalim.com 2014-now

- Writing for tips and tricks in programming

Github account: <a href="https://github.com/sendyhalim">https://github.com/sendyhalim</a>